export const flashcards = [
	{
		"id": 19,
		"category": "linux",
		"kind": "command",
		"front": "find out what kind of command a command is, e.g. `ls`",
		"back": "type ls",
		"extras": "",
		"pronunciation": "",
		"memoryHook": "",
		"memoryStory": "",
		"rank": "3.38",
		"labels": "",
		"status": "learned",
		"lastTested": "2019-08-31 07:08:18",
		"numberOfTimesTested": 1,
		"lastLearned": "2019-08-31 07:08:18",
		"numberOfTimesLearned": 1,
		"importId": "findOutWhatKindOfCommandACommandIsEgLs_typeLs",
		"systemWhenCreated": "2019-08-30 07:43:16",
		"systemWhoCreated": "systemUnknown"
	},
	{
		"id": 20,
		"category": "linux",
		"kind": "command",
		"front": "how to find out your shell\t\t",
		"back": "echo $0",
		"extras": "",
		"pronunciation": "",
		"memoryHook": "",
		"memoryStory": "",
		"rank": "2.5",
		"labels": "",
		"status": "learned",
		"lastTested": "2019-08-31 07:13:45",
		"numberOfTimesTested": 1,
		"lastLearned": "2019-08-31 07:13:45",
		"numberOfTimesLearned": 1,
		"importId": "howToFindOutYourShell_echo",
		"systemWhenCreated": "2019-08-30 07:43:16",
		"systemWhoCreated": "systemUnknown"
	},
	{
		"id": 21,
		"category": "linux",
		"kind": "command",
		"front": "how to get a detailed list of files in a directory",
		"back": "ll\t\t",
		"extras": "",
		"pronunciation": "",
		"memoryHook": "",
		"memoryStory": "",
		"rank": "2.84",
		"labels": "",
		"status": "learned",
		"lastTested": "2019-08-31 07:08:22",
		"numberOfTimesTested": 1,
		"lastLearned": "2019-08-31 07:08:22",
		"numberOfTimesLearned": 1,
		"importId": "howToGetADetailedListOfFilesInADirectory_ll",
		"systemWhenCreated": "2019-08-30 07:43:16",
		"systemWhoCreated": "systemUnknown"
	},
	{
		"id": 1658,
		"category": "git",
		"kind": "command",
		"front": "get back file from staging area to working directory, i.e. unstage a file",
		"back": "git reset [file]",
		"extras": "",
		"pronunciation": "",
		"memoryHook": "",
		"memoryStory": "",
		"rank": "4.73",
		"labels": "",
		"status": "learned",
		"lastTested": "2019-10-29 08:21:09",
		"numberOfTimesTested": 4,
		"lastLearned": "2019-10-29 08:21:09",
		"numberOfTimesLearned": 1,
		"importId": "getBackFileFromStagingAreaToWorkingDirectory_gitResetFile",
		"systemWhenCreated": "2019-10-29 05:48:34",
		"systemWhoCreated": "systemUnknown"
	},
	{
		"id": 1659,
		"category": "git",
		"kind": "command",
		"front": "show simplified log \"hash - title - author\"",
		"back": "git log --pretty=format:\"%h - %s - %an\" ",
		"extras": "",
		"pronunciation": "",
		"memoryHook": "",
		"memoryStory": "",
		"rank": "4.77",
		"labels": "",
		"status": "learned",
		"lastTested": "2020-05-06 08:58:02",
		"numberOfTimesTested": 9,
		"lastLearned": "2020-05-06 08:58:02",
		"numberOfTimesLearned": 1,
		"importId": "showSimplifiedLog_gitLogPrettyformathSAn",
		"systemWhenCreated": "2019-10-29 05:48:34",
		"systemWhoCreated": "systemUnknown"
	},
	{
		"id": 1660,
		"category": "git",
		"kind": "command",
		"front": "discard changes in working directory (before add)",
		"back": "git checkout -- [file]",
		"extras": "",
		"pronunciation": "",
		"memoryHook": "",
		"memoryStory": "",
		"rank": "4.64",
		"labels": "",
		"status": "learned",
		"lastTested": "2019-10-29 07:14:06",
		"numberOfTimesTested": 2,
		"lastLearned": "2019-10-29 07:14:06",
		"numberOfTimesLearned": 1,
		"importId": "discardChangesInWorkingDirectoryBeforeAdd_gitCheckoutFile",
		"systemWhenCreated": "2019-10-29 05:48:34",
		"systemWhoCreated": "systemUnknown"
	},
	{
		"id": 1661,
		"category": "git",
		"kind": "command",
		"front": "remove file from working directory and add deletion to staging area",
		"back": "git rm [file]",
		"extras": "",
		"pronunciation": "",
		"memoryHook": "",
		"memoryStory": "",
		"rank": "4.74",
		"labels": "",
		"status": "learned",
		"lastTested": "2019-10-29 07:43:38",
		"numberOfTimesTested": 2,
		"lastLearned": "2019-10-29 07:43:38",
		"numberOfTimesLearned": 1,
		"importId": "removeFileFromWorkingDirectoryAndAddDeletionToStagingArea_gitRmFile",
		"systemWhenCreated": "2019-10-29 06:33:19",
		"systemWhoCreated": "systemUnknown"
	},
	{
		"id": 1662,
		"category": "git",
		"kind": "command",
		"front": "how to find out what the master is",
		"back": "git remote show origin",
		"extras": "",
		"pronunciation": "",
		"memoryHook": "",
		"memoryStory": "",
		"rank": "3.79",
		"labels": "",
		"status": "learned",
		"lastTested": "2020-06-08 06:03:08",
		"numberOfTimesTested": 5,
		"lastLearned": "2020-06-08 06:03:08",
		"numberOfTimesLearned": 1,
		"importId": "howToFindOutWhatTheMasterIs_gitRemoteShowOriginYouHaveToLogin",
		"systemWhenCreated": "2019-10-29 06:33:19",
		"systemWhoCreated": "systemUnknown"
	},
	{
		"id": 1663,
		"category": "git",
		"kind": "command",
		"front": "list operations made on local repository",
		"back": "git reflog",
		"extras": "",
		"pronunciation": "",
		"memoryHook": "",
		"memoryStory": "",
		"rank": "2.76",
		"labels": "",
		"status": "testing",
		"lastTested": "2019-11-29 02:16:14",
		"numberOfTimesTested": 2,
		"lastLearned": "",
		"numberOfTimesLearned": 0,
		"importId": "listOperationsMadeOnLocalRepository_gitReflog",
		"systemWhenCreated": "2019-10-29 06:33:19",
		"systemWhoCreated": "systemUnknown"
	},
	{
		"id": 1667,
		"category": "git",
		"kind": "command",
		"front": "change user name",
		"back": "git config --global user.name \"Hans Schmidt\"",
		"extras": "",
		"pronunciation": "",
		"memoryHook": "",
		"memoryStory": "",
		"rank": "4.5",
		"labels": "",
		"status": "learned",
		"lastTested": "2019-11-27 11:11:35",
		"numberOfTimesTested": 10,
		"lastLearned": "2019-11-27 11:11:35",
		"numberOfTimesLearned": 1,
		"importId": "changeUserName_gitConfigGlobalUsernameHansSchmidt",
		"systemWhenCreated": "2019-10-29 08:20:51",
		"systemWhoCreated": "systemUnknown"
	}
];